export const Question = [
    {question: 'is a multidisciplinary field that focuses on the design and use of computer technology, particularly the interfaces between people (users) and computers', answer : 'human computer interaction'},
    {question: '-MEMEX by Vanera Bush', answer : '1945'},
    {question: 'Sketchpad and light pen by ivan sutherland', answer: '1963'},
    {question: 'Mouse by Doug Engelbert', answer: '1964'},
    {question: 'Alto by Xerox Park', answer: '1973'},
    {question: 'Apple Lisa', answer: '1983'},
    {question: 'Windows', answer: '1987'},
    {question: 'They are limited in their capacity to process information ', answer: 'Humans'},
    {question: 'any technology that people interact with, including desktop computers, mobile phones, and computer systems', answer: 'Computer'},
    {question: 'HCI is concerned with joint performance of task by humand and computer', answer: 'Interaction'},
    {question: 'The main goal of HCI', answer: 'Usability'},
    {question: 'Is the processing of information', answer: 'Cognition'},
    {question: 'Combines real and virtual Realities', answer: 'Augmented Reality'},
    {question: 'Immerses the viewer into computer generated environments ', answer: 'Virtual Reality'},
    {question: 'Virtual and real environment are opposite ends of this continuum \n Ar is closer to the real world ', answer: 'Reality Continuum'},
    {question: 'Morton Heilig, Sensorama', answer: '1957-1962'},
    {question: 'Ivan Sutherland, head Mounted Display', answer: '1966'},
    {question: 'Myron Krueg, Videplace ', answer: '1975'},
    {question: 'Jaron Lanier Coined the term Virtual Reality', answer: '1989'},
    {question: 'Tom Caudeli Coined the term Augmented Reality', answer: '1992'},
    {question: 'Julie Martin, AR Theater', answer: '1994'},
    {question: 'Hirokazu Kato, AR toolkit ', answer: '1999'},
    {question: 'Bruce Thomas, AR Quake', answer: '2000'},
    {question: 'Wikitude, AR Travel Guide and Navigation System', answer: '2008 - 2009'},
    {question: 'AR toolkit Ported to adobe Flash.', answer: '2009'},
    {question: 'Combines and displays physical world images and virtual graphical objects', answer: 'Head Mounted / Heads-Up Displays'},
    {question: 'Small handheld computing devices \n Uses Global  Positioning System', answer: 'Handlheld Displays'},
    {question: 'Uses digital projector to display information', answer: 'Spatial Devices'},
    {question: 'Promotes via interactive AR application', answer: 'Advertising Application'},
    {question: 'Marketing consumers on location with ratings, reviews and other information', answer: 'Marketing Application'},
    {question: 'Compare the data of digital mock-ups with physical mock-ups \n Provde insutrctions, specs, and training for mechanics operators', answer: 'Industrial Application'},
    {question: 'visualize 3d phenomena \n Display interactive analysis of terrain characteristics', answer: 'Scientific Application'},
    {question: 'Create over real art \n Simulate Construction projects \n Create virtual Objects on locations  ', answer: 'Art Application'},
    {question: 'Provide poweful contextual, explorative and discovery learning experiences \n Teach Critical Thinking, science and social studies through ar gaming ', answer: 'Educational Application'},
    {question: 'Learners use mobile devices to gain knowledge', answer: 'Mobile learning'},
    {question: 'Large margin of error ', answer: 'Accuracy'},
    {question: 'no one open among ar browsers ', answer: 'Standards'},
    {question: 'availability of ar capable devices ', answer: 'Smartphones only'},
    {question: 'Learners use distant network servers for web application m', answer: 'Cloud Computing'},
    {question: 'Learning goes beyond space and time ', answer: 'Community-Community Interaction'},
    {question: 'Learners get real time , up to date information  ', answer: 'Aggretion'},
    {question: 'Learners combine online content with online resources to enfance learning ', answer: 'Mash up'},
    {question: 'Learners apply visualization (2d to 3d) to enchanc e learning ', answer: 'Info-viz'},

]


export const Enum = [ 
    {title:'User Interaction Design' , enumerate: [
        'Data Collection', 
        'Data Analysis',
        'User Modeling', 
        'Design',
        'Prototype',
        'Evaluation'
    ]},
    {title: 'Interaction Styles', enumerate : [
      'Command Line Interface',
       'WIMP',
       'Question and Answer Dialouge' ,
       'Fill Form Interface',
       'Menus',
       'Direct Manipulation',
      'Natural language'
    ]}
    ,
    {title:'Future', enumerate : 
        ['Artificial Intelligence',
            'Virtual Reality',
            'New Interface Devices'
        ]
    },
    {title:'Input Devices', enumerate : 
        [
            'Keyboard',
            'Mouse,TrackBalls, Touch Pads',
            'Touch Screens',
            'Speech Input' ,
            '3d Trackers, 3d Mouse', 
    
        ]
    },
    {title:'Processing of information ', enumerate : 
        [
            'Perception', 
            'Attention',
            'Pattern Matching', 
            'Memory',
            'Language Processing', 
            'Decision Making', 
            'Problem Solving'
        
        ]
    },
    {title:'Goals', enumerate : 
        [
            'Easy to Learn',
            'Easy to remember how to use',
            'Effective to use',
            'Efficient to use',
            'Safe to use',
            'Enjoyable to use' 
        
        ]
    },
    {title:'Three Main Cognitive Challenges', enumerate : 
        [
            'Conceptual Complexity',
            'Memory Load', 
            'Attention' 
        
            
        ]
    },
    {title:'Display Types', enumerate : 
        [
            'Head-Mounted, or heads-up, display',
           'Handheld displays',
           'Spatial displays'
            
        ]
    },
    {title:'input and output channels', enumerate : 
        [
           'Visual Channel',
            'Auditory Channel',
            'Haptic Channel' ,
            'Movement'
            
        ]
    },
    {title:'Information is stored in memory', enumerate : 
        [
            'Sensory Memory',
            'Working Memory',
            'Long-Term Memory'

            
        ]
    },
    {title:'Pending/ Future application ', enumerate : 
        [
            'Expanding PC Screen into real world' ,
            '‘Holodecks’',
           'Replacement of cellphone and vehicle navigation screen',
            'Virtual Everything' ,
            'Virutal Gadgetry',
            'Subscriptions to group specific AR Feeds' ,
            'Virtual Retinal Displays',
            'AR-enabled contact lenses'
        ]
    },
    
    
   
]